[{
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='E_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Em",
        "wrongAnswer1": "D",
        "wrongAnswer2": "G",
        "wrongAnswer3": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "D",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Em",
        "wrongAnswer2": "G",
        "wrongAnswer3": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "G",
        "wrongAnswer1": "D",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Em",
        "wrongAnswer3": "C"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='C' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "C",
        "wrongAnswer1": "D",
        "wrongAnswer2": "G",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Em"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Dm",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='E' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "E",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Eadd9",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Bm7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Gm",
        "wrongAnswer1": "B7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A#",
        "wrongAnswer3": "C#m"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='B_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Bm",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer2": "B7",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Cm7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='B_7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "B7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Em7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A#m7",
        "wrongAnswer3": "C#m7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A_m7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Am7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Em7",
        "wrongAnswer2": "F#",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Cadd9"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='F_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "Fm",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E#m",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Badd9",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F#"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='A#_add9' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "A#add9",
        "wrongAnswer1": "B",
        "wrongAnswer2": "C",
        "wrongAnswer3": "D"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='C' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "C",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "B"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "D",
        "wrongAnswer1": "B",
        "wrongAnswer2": "C#",
        "wrongAnswer3": "A"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='G#' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "G#",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E#",
        "wrongAnswer2": "A7",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F#m"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D#_m' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "D#m",
        "wrongAnswer1": "Bm",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Cm",
        "wrongAnswer3": "Dm7"
    },
    {
        "question": "<canvas class='chord' chord='D#_7' width='180' height='200'></canvas>",
        "rightAnswer": "D#7",
        "wrongAnswer1": "E",
        "wrongAnswer2": "Am",
        "wrongAnswer3": "F"
    }
]